A Guide to the Office of University Relations, General Correspondence File of William Hillman Wranek, Director, University New Service, 1916-1961
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of University Relations, General Correspondence File of William Hillman Wranek, Director, University New Service 1916-1961
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/1.491
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1976 December 22.
Contents List
- General Correspondence 1916 Jun-1930 Feb (Box 1)
- General Correspondence (5 folders) 1930-1938 (Box 1)
- General Correspondence (6 folders) 1938-1944 (Box 2)
- General Correspondence (7 folders) 1945-1948 (Box 3)
- General Correspondence (8 folders) 1949-1951 (Box 4)
- General Correspondence (10 folders) 1951-1955 (Box 5)
- General Correspondence (5 folders) 1955-1960 (Box 6)
- Budget, Public Relations n.d. (Box 6)
- Personnel 1956-1961 (Box 6)
- General Correspondence 1961 Jan-Dec (Box 6)
- General Correspondence (2 folders) n.d. (Box 6)